Thanks for coming.
Go grab a seat.
Wait!
Severin, have you lost your mind?!
This is the Holy
Cathedral, not a damn mine!
They’re my friends.
Got a problem with that?
Hell yes I do!
My daughter married
into nobility,
not to some loser who
hangs with dirt-diggers!
There's nothing wrong with miners.
Their blood's just
as red as yours.
Maybe.
But they're not your equals.
The Scott family won't
be dirtied by scum.
Either they leave,
or there's no wedding!
I told you
we never should have
let Livia marry this worthless fool.
Who knew the eldest
son of House Carter would
turn out to be
such a complete failure.
These men worked side by side with my son.
They mean well.
Please, let it go.
Absolutely not!
If these filthy losers
don’t get out right now,
this wedding is canceled!
It’s cool, Severin.
We’ll head out.
We’re too dirty
for this place anyway.
Congrats.
Yeah, congrats, Severin.
We’ll take off.
Ugh, little bug, move away.
Trash. Go back where you belong.
Finally,
they're leaving.
No one leaves today!